<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<!--
 * RapidEnv: ConfigFile.xml
 *
 * Copyright (C) 2010 Martin Bluemel
 *
 * Creation Date: 09/08/2010
 *
 * This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the
 * GNU Lesser General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation;
 * either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
 * This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY;
 * without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
 * See the GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.
 * You should have received a copies of the GNU Lesser General Public License and the
 * GNU General Public License along with this program; if not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->

<beantype name="org.rapidbeans.rapidenv.config.file.ConfigFile"
	extends="org.rapidbeans.rapidenv.config.Configuration">

	<description>An configuration operation on a single file</description>

	<property name="path" type="string"
		mandatory="true" mustexist="false"
		propclass="org.rapidbeans.rapidenv.config.PropertyInterpretedString">
		<description>The path to the file to configure. The path usually is a relative one.
If it is relative it is supposed to be relative to the parent installation unit's home directory.</description>
	</property>

	<property name="sourceurl" type="string"
		propclass="org.rapidbeans.rapidenv.config.PropertyInterpretedString">
		<description>Defines where the file to configure comes from.
If "sourceurl" is not defined the file to configure is supposed to be already
existent and will only be changed from its original form.</description>
	</property>

    <property name="deleteafterdeinstall" type="boolean"
        default="true">
        <description>Determines if the configuration file should be deleted
after deinstallation in case it is not under the installation root.
In the case it is under the installation root it will be deleted anyway.
Set this value to false if you want to prevent this default behavior.</description>
    </property>

    <property name="newline" type="choice"
        enum="NewlineType" default="platform">
        <description>Defines the newline character(s) to use.</description>
    </property>

    <property name="canread" type="boolean"
        default="true">
        <description>Determines if the file to configure can be read
(default = true).</description>
    </property>

    <property name="canwrite" type="boolean"
        default="true">
        <description>Determines if the file to configure can be written
(default = true).</description>
    </property>

	<property name="canexecute" type="boolean"
		default="false">
        <description>Determines if the file to configure can be executed
(default = false).</description>
	</property>

	<property name="copycondition" type="choice"
		enum="FileCopyCondition"
		default="sourcenewer">
		<description>The condition when the source is copied over the target:
notexist:    when the target does not exist
sourcenewer: when the source is new than the target: allows manual and
             automatic change aftwerwards but ensures template changes
			 being processed
diff:        strict binding to the source file (manual changes are excluded)</description>
	</property>

	<property name="encoding" type="choice"
		enum="org.rapidbeans.datasource.CharsetsAvailable"
		default="UTF-8">
		<description>One of the following text file encodings: Big5, Big5-HKSCS, EUC-JP, EUC-KR, GB18030, GB2312, GBK, IBM-Thai,
		IBM00858, IBM01140, IBM01141, IBM01142, IBM01143, IBM01144, IBM01145, IBM01146, IBM01147, IBM01148, IBM01149, IBM037,
		IBM1026, IBM1047, IBM273, IBM277, IBM278, IBM280, IBM284, IBM285, IBM297, IBM420, IBM424, IBM437, IBM500, IBM775, IBM850,
		IBM852, IBM855, IBM857, IBM860, IBM861, IBM862, IBM863, IBM864, IBM865, IBM866, IBM868, IBM869, IBM870, IBM871, IBM918,
		ISO-2022-CN, ISO-2022-JP, ISO-2022-JP-2, ISO-2022-KR, ISO-8859-1, ISO-8859-13, ISO-8859-15, ISO-8859-2, ISO-8859-3, ISO-8859-4,
		ISO-8859-5, ISO-8859-6, ISO-8859-7, ISO-8859-8, ISO-8859-9, JIS_X0201, JIS_X0212-1990, KOI8-R, KOI8-U, Shift_JIS, TIS-620,
		US-ASCII, UTF-16, UTF-16BE, UTF-16LE, UTF-32, UTF-32BE, UTF-32LE, UTF-8, windows-1250, windows-1251, windows-1252, windows-1253,
		windows-1254, windows-1255, windows-1256, windows-1257, windows-1258, windows-31j,
		x-Big5-HKSCS-2001, x-Big5-Solaris, x-euc-jp-linux, x-EUC-TW, x-eucJP-Open, x-IBM1006, x-IBM1025, x-IBM1046, x-IBM1097,
		x-IBM1098, x-IBM1112, x-IBM1122, x-IBM1123, x-IBM1124, x-IBM1381, x-IBM1383, x-IBM33722, x-IBM737, x-IBM833, x-IBM834,
		x-IBM856, x-IBM874, x-IBM875, x-IBM921, x-IBM922, x-IBM930, x-IBM933, x-IBM935, x-IBM937, x-IBM939, x-IBM942, x-IBM942C,
		x-IBM943, x-IBM943C, x-IBM948, x-IBM949, x-IBM949C, x-IBM950, x-IBM964, x-IBM970, x-ISCII91, x-ISO-2022-CN-CNS, x-ISO-2022-CN-GB,
		x-iso-8859-11, x-JIS0208, x-JISAutoDetect, x-Johab, x-MacArabic, x-MacCentralEurope, x-MacCroatian, x-MacCyrillic, x-MacDingbat,
		x-MacGreek, x-MacHebrew, x-MacIceland, x-MacRoman, x-MacRomania, x-MacSymbol, x-MacThai, x-MacTurkish, x-MacUkraine, x-MS932_0213,
		x-MS950-HKSCS, x-MS950-HKSCS-XP, x-mswin-936, x-PCK, x-SJIS_0213, x-UTF-16LE-BOM, X-UTF-32BE-BOM, X-UTF-32LE-BOM, x-windows-50220,
		x-windows-50221, x-windows-874, x-windows-949, x-windows-950, x-windows-iso2022jp</description>
	</property>

	<property name="tasks" type="association"
		composition="true"
		targettype="org.rapidbeans.rapidenv.config.ConfigurationTask">
		<description>Tasks serve to extend the configuration.</description>
	</property>

	<property name="commandonconfig" type="association"
		composition="true"
		targettype="org.rapidbeans.rapidenv.config.cmd.SystemCommand"
		maxmult="1"
		>
		<description>Defines a system command that is automatically
executed whenever a configuration on this file or folder has been performed</description>
	</property>

	<codegen mode="split"/>
</beantype>
